// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " What kind of energy is converted in a galvanic cell?",
    answer: "Chemical energy is converted into electrical energy.",
    options: [
      "Chemical energy is converted into electrical energy.",
      "Chemical energy is converted to heat.",
      "Chemical energy is obtained from heat.",
      "Electrical energy is converted into chemical energy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The most abundant metal on the surface of the earth is",
    answer: "Al",
    options: [
      " Fe",
      "Al",
      "Ca",
      "Na"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following would react to form pentylethanoate?",
    answer: "1-pentanol and ethanoic acid",
    options: [
      "1-propanol and pentanoic acid",
      "Ethanol and pentanoic acid",
      "1-pentanol and ethanoic acid",
      "Ethanol and ethanoic acid"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What Which of the following ionic compounds has the greatest lattice energy?",
    answer: "LiF",
    options: [
      "LiF",
      "LiCl",
      "LiBr",
      "LiI"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The first step of the scientific method involves",
    answer: "Making observations.",
    options: [
      "Forming a hypothesis.",
      "Making observations.",
      "Performing an experiment",
      "Predicting the result of an experiment."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is a natural polymer ? ",
    answer: "Cellulose",
    options: [
      "Keratin",
      "Polythene",
      "Cellulose",
      "Polymethyl methacrylate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the solvent in 70% alcohol solution ? ",
    answer: "Water",
    options: [
      "Water",
      "Alcohol",
      "Sugar",
      "Kerosene"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following are NOT electromagnetic waves? ",
    answer: "Sound waves",
    options: [
      "Infrared waves",
      "Gamma waves",
      "Radio waves",
      "Sound waves"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What type of solute-solvent interaction should be the most important in a solution of iodine in carbon tetrachloride? ",
    answer: "London forces",
    options: [
      "London forces",
      "Ionic bonding",
      "Ion-dipole forces",
      "Dipole-dipole forces"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which one of the following is NOT a form of chemical bonding? ",
    answer: "Hydrogen bonding",
    options: [
      " Covalent bonding",
      "Metallic bonding",
      "Ionic bonding",
      "Hydrogen bonding"
    ]
  },






];